jacobbromwell.com 2016-03-24

# Privacy Policy | Jacob Bromwell®

## PRIVACY POLICY - THE BROMWELL COMPANY  

Rev: 8/28/2013

## GENERAL

* * *

The Bromwell Company ("Bromwell") respects the privacy of every individual who visits bromwell.com, jacobbromwell.com, trizenium.com, and luovasales.com (the "Websites") or responds to our guestbook, contests, or interactive advertisements. Bromwell's Privacy Policy outlines the information Bromwell will collect and how we will use that information. This Policy will also inform you what to do if you do not want your Personal Information to be shared or divulged when you visit our Website or respond to our advertising.

We do not attempt to collect excessive or irrelevant information, whether that information personally identifies you or not. We collect information solely for the purposes stated below. We will take reasonable steps to delete or de-identify information about you that we collect when it is no longer needed to interact with you. You agree that until you notify us by following the instructions under "Opt-out" below or we determine that the information is no longer needed, we may retain the information indefinitely.

We do not knowingly collect, use or retain any information from any person submitting information to us from any location outside of the United States and its Territories.

By using our Website you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any terms or practices described in this Privacy Policy please do not use our Website.

## PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

* * *

Bromwell will not collect any Personal Information about you (that is your name, address, telephone number, or email address) unless you provide it voluntarily. If you do not want your Personal Information collected do not submit it to us.

If you do submit Personal Information we will store and process that information to better understand your needs, offer certain products and services in connection with our Website; communicate to you; provide customer service; provide a personalized shopping experience; prevent fraud; fulfill your orders, including delivery and billing; complete payment method processing and improve our products and services.

We may also use that information or provide it to outside companies to contact you; provide that information to partners to enable you to access those partners' websites; and aggregate the data you provide to us with other publicly available data about you.

We will not distribute or sell your Personal Information to any outside company for marketing or solicitation of any product not affiliated with Bromwell and your Personal Information will only be used to support your relationship with Bromwell and its partners. In each case, the outside company is under agreement with Bromwell to protect your Personal Information and to use it solely as Bromwell directs.

There are certain limited instances where we may disclose or transfer Personal Information other than as described above. For example, we may provide such information to appropriate authorities if we believe in good faith that the law requires it or to protect our legal rights or property. Additionally, as we continue to develop our business, we may buy or sell business assets. In such transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferred business assets. However, we are not in the business of selling customer information to others, and aside from certain exceptional circumstances, we will take appropriate measures to ensure the protection of the information you provide to us.

## AGGREGATING THIRD PARTY INFORMATION WITH PERSONAL INFORMATION

* * *

We may, either through our own searches or by contact with third party providers, add publicly available information to the Personal Information you elect to provide to us. For example, if you provide your name or address, we may add your telephone number and email address to your Personal Information. We will treat any information that personally identifies you, including any such information that we add to your Personal Information as your Personal Information and subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

## CHANGING MY PERSONAL INFORMATION

* * *

We take reasonable steps to ensure that all of your Personal Information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete, up to date, stored in a secure environment and accessed only be authorized personnel for permitted purposes. If your Personal Information changes, you may update/register your information on the Web page titled "Register Here". You may also contact us using the information in "Contact Us" below to review the Personal Information you provided, update your Personal Information or request that we remove your Personal Information from our records. If you request, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete your Personal Information from our existing records.

## CHILDREN (UNDER EIGHTEEN)

* * *

We do not knowingly collect, use or retain any Personal Information from visitors to our Website who are under eighteen (18) years of age for any purpose whatsoever (including internal or external marketing purposes). Where appropriate, we will instruct children not to submit information to our Website or advertisements. We will delete any records of any such Personal Information that comes to our attention. If it comes to your attention that your child under 18 has provided any Personal Information to our Website, we invite you to notify us by following the instructions under "Opt-out" below or by contacting us via the "Contact Us" section of our Website so that we may delete the information from our records and discontinue any related features or services.

While our policy prohibits the collection of information from children under 18, parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a kid-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from disclosing online their name, address and other personal information without parental permission. For additional information about parental control tools, please consult the "Consumer Assistance" page of the Direct Marketing Association home page.

## NON-PERSONALLY - IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION COLLECTED AUTOMATICALLY

* * *

In general, you can visit our Website and view its content while remaining anonymous by not providing any Personal Information. In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not Personal Information. Examples of this type of information include the Internet browser you are using, the type of operating system, the domain name of the website which linked you to our site, the pages you visited while you were using our Website, the domain name of the website you next go to, and your Internet Protocol address. When collected, we use non-personally identifiable information to determine the overall reaction to various sections of our Website(the length and frequency of stays at our Website and the variety of searches of our Website's database), measure the effectiveness and usefulness of various pages (how our Website is navigated, how many visitors arrive at specific pages), and to improve the flow and interconnectivity of the site.

When you view our Website we may also store information from time to time on your computer. This information is stored in the form of "Cookies". "Cookies" allow us to tailor our Website or advertisement to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers you can block, receive a warning or erase all "Cookies" from your hard drive. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. If you choose not to accept "Cookies", you should be aware that you might not be able to experience the full functionality of our Website. The data on your use of our Website may be linked to the Personal Information you have chosen to share with us when you register.

## LINKS AND PRIVACY

* * *

We may provide links to websites outside of our Website. These linked sites are outside of our control, and we are not responsible for the conduct of companies linked to our Website.

## OPT-OUT

* * *

If after registering on or otherwise providing your Personal Information when visiting our Website you no longer wish to receive any materials, offers or correspondence, please send an email to [service@bromwell.com](mailto:service@bromwell.com), indicating your preference to "unsubscribe" and we will promptly remove you from our list. Please be sure to include your name and email address in your email. You can also submit your opt-out request through this self-service form, email opt-out.

## CONTACT US

* * *

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy or would like to have any Personal Information updated or deleted from our records please contact us at: [service@bromwell.com](mailto:service@bromwell.com)

## HOW TO PROTECT THE SECURITY OF YOUR FINANCIAL INFORMATION

* * *

The security of your financial information is very important to us. In our efforts to protect your online transactions, we use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). If your browser is capable of (SSL) (and most are), your financial information will be automatically encrypted, or encoded, before it is sent over the Internet.

Our Website has also obtained a digital certificate from Verisign, Inc., a leading provider of Internet trust services. When you enter a secure portion of our site (which is any page containing any of your financial information), an image of a closed lock or a solid key should appear in the bottom bar of your browser window. If you click on this image, a small popup window displaying site-security information will appear. The certificate guarantees that your financial information is being transmitted in secure (encrypted) form to our Website Web server, not to some unknown or unauthorized server.

Ultimately, your financial information is protected by the password you created when you created an account at JacobBromwell.com (or another password you chose after changing a previous password). Please keep this password confidential. No Customer Service Associate or any other representative of Bromwell will ever ask you for your password. The confidentiality of your password is yours to protect. You may change it anytime by going to "User Registration". Log in with your email address and password, then click "Continue" and enter a new password.

## CHANGES TO THE POLICY

* * *

Please check this privacy policy periodically to inform yourself of any changes. Although we reserve the right to modify or supplement this privacy policy, we will provide notice to you on this Website of any major changes for at least 30 days following the change.
